Napul Labde

Opposite of 40 quater Akola, Maharastra, India

📳 +919370486496 | 💌 napul.labde21@pccoepune.org | 👑 September 29th, 2002 | 🖸 github.com/napul205 | 🛅 linkedin.com/in/napul-labde/

Summary.

I'm a third-year computer engineering student who is enthusiastic about using technology to address issues in the real world. I have a solid background in computer engineering. I also have experience with programming languages like Java, Python, and C++ in the real world. I have a strong interest in web development and machine learning, and I have worked on research projects in these areas.

Education

PCET'S Pimpri Chinchwad College Of Engineering

Pune, India

B.tech in Computer Engineering

dec 2021 - Current

- · pursuing
- 3rd year student

Government Polytechnic Amravati

Amaravati, India

Aug 2018 - may 2021

Diploma in Computer Engineering

• Complete

• Marks: 93.26

Work Experience _____

ERP Launchpad Pune, India

Intern jan 2023 - feb 2023

as an intern from January 2023 to February 2023 at Google, I utilized Google App Script to automate various functionalities inside Google Sheets.
This included creating web applications and working on backend logic development, creating login logic, and fetching data in the web app from Google Sheets.

• My technical skills in this role included Google AppScript, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Furthermore, I demonstrated strong soft skills such as teamwork, time management, communication, and presentation skills.

Skills_

Programming C/C++, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, SQL, Java, React.js . **Miscellaneous** Linux, Shell (Bash/Zsh) Microsoft Office, Git.

Soft Skills Time Management, Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation.

Achievements

2016	3rd on district level , Open Side 10 meter Air Rifel shooting	India
2023	250+ problem solved on, Leetcode	India
2023	2 Star on, CodeChef	India

Publications

JOURNAL ARTICLES

A Review on Real-Time Traffic Sign Recognition with Voice Warnings Harsh Wangikar, Priya Surana, Prakash Sawant, Napul Labde, Akshat Shah Mat Journals 1.3 (Dec. 2022) pp. 5–12. 2022

Interests_

Art I have always enjoyed drawing since I was a child.

Video Games I always had the gaming gene. I mostly play on my phone and occasionally on my switch.

Swimming I started swimming when I was 12. Going through submerged things while holding my breath was the most exciting part.

Languages

English Professional proficiency **Marathi** Native proficiency

APRIL 14, 2023 1